[SHAPE YOUR FUTURE]
[AI] [塑造你的未来]
For me. public space is political.
[AI] 为了我。公共空间是政治性的。
I work with communities around the world.
[AI] 我与世界各地的社区合作。
and as we know. every community has problems.
[AI] 正如我们所知。每个社区都有问题。
Some of these problems are solved through the ballot box
[AI] 其中一些问题是通过投票箱解决的
or city hall meetings
[AI] 或市政厅会议
or community efforts. like bike lanes and potholes and school budgets.
[AI] 或社区努力。比如自行车道、坑洼和学校预算。
But some problems are beyond the reach of these structures.
[AI] 但有些问题是这些机构无法解决的。
like food deserts.
[AI] 就像食物沙漠。
community well-being
[AI] 社区福利
and the loss of cultural identity.
[AI] 文化身份的丧失。
These problems cannot be solved with the existing tool sets.
[AI] 使用现有的工具集无法解决这些问题。
I believe that public space is the most potent place to discuss these issues.
[AI] 我相信公共空间是讨论这些问题的最有力的场所。
because it contains the richest diversity of perspectives.
[AI] 因为它包含了丰富多样的观点。
And that's what makes it so powerful.
[AI] 这就是它如此强大的原因。
The existing parks. town squares and sidewalks are not enough. though.
[AI] 现有的公园。城市广场和人行道是不够的。虽然
which is why I'm interested in creating a new type of public space.
[AI] 这就是为什么我对创造一种新型的公共空间感兴趣。
one that's built by the community and designed specifically for their needs.
[AI] 一个由社区建立并专门为他们的需要而设计的社区。
I start by listening
[AI] 我从听开始
and by setting up actual outdoor living rooms.
[AI] 通过设置实际的室外客厅。
complete with couches. tables. chairs. rugs and lamps.
[AI] 配有沙发。桌子。椅子。地毯和灯。
as a way of holding meetings to learn about the issues
[AI] 作为召开会议了解问题的一种方式
directly from the community.
[AI] 直接来自社区。
I use this technique to capture the voices and ideas of people
[AI] 我用这种技巧捕捉人们的声音和想法
that might not have time or feel comfortable in more formal meetings.
[AI] 在更正式的会议上，他们可能没有时间或感觉不舒服。
So why get someone to sit in a love seat in the middle of the street?
[AI] 那么，为什么要让人坐在街中间的一个爱情座椅上呢？
In York. Alabama. the residents bear witness
[AI] 在约克。阿拉巴马州。居民作证
to the abandoned houses that cover the town.
[AI] 到覆盖全城的废弃房屋。
which are a constant reminder of the white flight that took place
[AI] 这是一个持续的白色飞行发生的提醒
after segregation ended.
[AI] 隔离结束后。
when white homeowners left the area and let their houses fall into disrepair.
[AI] 当白人房主离开该地区，让他们的房子年久失修时。
Teaming up with the people of York.
[AI] 与约克人合作。
we transformed an iconic. pink-sided. blighted property in the middle of town
[AI] 我们改造了一座标志性建筑。粉红色的。城中失地的财产
into a new house. called "Open House."
[AI] 搬进一所新房子。叫做“开放日”
However. this house has a secret.
[AI] 然而这房子有个秘密。
It physically transforms into a 100-seat open-air theater for plays. movies. music
[AI] 它实际上变成了一个有100个座位的露天剧场。电影。音乐
or whatever the community would like to experience.
[AI] 或者社区想要体验的任何东西。
And when it folds back up into the shape of a house.
[AI] 当它折叠成房子的形状时。
the image of the reclaimed pink siding reminds people of the past.
[AI] 回收的粉红色墙板的图像让人们想起了过去。
After its opening. the mayor saw the potential in Open House
[AI] 开幕后。市长看到了开放日的潜力
and held the next town hall meeting there.
[AI] 并在那里举行了下一次市政厅会议。
The excitement of this unique gathering space brought new energy
[AI] 这个独特的聚集空间带来了新的活力
and gave a fresh viewpoint to collectively discuss the future of the town.
[AI] 并提出了一个全新的观点来集体讨论该镇的未来。
In Cambridge. Massachusetts.
[AI] 在剑桥。马萨诸塞州。
to highlight the issues of energy. waste and climate change.
[AI] 突出能源问题。废物和气候变化。
we replaced a garbage can in a park with an anaerobic digester
[AI] 我们把公园里的垃圾桶换成了厌氧消化器
to transform dog waste into usable methane gas.
[AI] 将狗粪转化为可用的甲烷气体。
Burning this methane lights the park
[AI] 燃烧甲烷照亮了公园
and reduces greenhouse gases.
[AI] 减少温室气体排放。
By slightly changing an everyday experience in public space.
[AI] 通过稍微改变公共空间的日常体验。
the Park Spark Project provokes neighbors to have conversations
[AI] 公园星火项目激发了邻居们的对话
about the natural and built systems around them
[AI] 关于他们周围的自然和建筑系统
and their connection to the environment.
[AI] 以及它们与环境的联系。
In Lyons. Nebraska. residents spoke about the loss of social life
[AI] 在里昂。内布拉斯加州。居民们谈到了社会生活的损失
as downtown storefronts began to shutter their doors.
[AI] 市中心的店面开始关门。
a result of the slow violence of disinvestment.
[AI] 这是缓慢的撤资暴力的结果。
which has left many rural downtowns empty.
[AI] 这使得许多郊区的市中心空无一人。
To address this loss of human connection.
[AI] 解决这种人际关系缺失的问题。
we used an abandoned storefront to turn Main Street into a movie theater.
[AI] 我们用一个废弃的店面把大街变成了电影院。
The storefront wall is modified with hydraulics
[AI] 店面的墙是用液压装置改造的
so that the awning and false front fold down over the sidewalk
[AI] 这样遮阳篷和假正面就可以在人行道上向下折叠
with the push of a button.
[AI] 只需按一下按钮。
providing seating for 100.
[AI] 提供100人的座位。
As the community came together to build a storefront theater.
[AI] 当社区聚在一起建造一个店面剧院时。
an eccentric postman who makes sci-fi movies starring his cat
[AI] 一个古怪的邮递员，以他的猫为主角制作科幻电影
proposed to make a documentary for the debut.
[AI] 提议为首映做一部纪录片。
And so that summer. we turned downtown into a movie set
[AI] 那年夏天也是如此。我们把市中心变成了电影场景
and the townspeople into actors
[AI] 镇上的人变成了演员
to create the movie "Decades." a history of Lyons downtown
[AI] 创作电影《十年》里昂市中心的历史
from its founding to the present moment.
[AI] 从成立到现在。
On opening night. the main street.
[AI] 在开幕之夜。主街。
which is usually empty after dark.
[AI] 天黑后通常是空的。
filled with people to watch the story of their town.
[AI] 挤满了人观看他们小镇的故事。
leaving locals to question:
[AI] 让当地人质疑：
How will we write the next chapter of Lyons?
[AI] 我们将如何写里昂的下一章？
Well. the next chapter started with a series of movie screenings.
[AI] 好下一章从一系列电影放映开始。
public events and international musicians.
[AI] 公共活动和国际音乐家。
as well as a low-budget film community that has blossomed in Lyons.
[AI] 以及在里昂蓬勃发展的低成本电影社区。
bringing in people from all over the world
[AI] 从世界各地引进人才
and a permanent art gallery that has opened next door.
[AI] 还有一个永久性的艺术画廊在隔壁开放。
My work harnesses the power of the built environment
[AI] 我的工作利用了建筑环境的力量
to focus on issues that communities and local governments
[AI] 关注社区和地方政府关注的问题
have failed to address themselves.
[AI] 他们没有解决自己的问题。
by creating projects so custom fit
[AI] 通过创建自定义适合的项目
that the community naturally makes it their own.
[AI] 社区自然会让它成为自己的。
When people from all walks of life have a shared experience in these spaces.
[AI] 当来自各行各业的人们在这些空间有着共同的经历时。
it can lead to a paradigm shift in how we see our home.
[AI] 这可能导致我们看待家的方式发生范式转变。
our community and the world.
[AI] 我们的社区和世界。
For me. public space is political
[AI] 为了我。公共空间是政治性的
and becomes powerful when it sparks people's imagination to envision
[AI] 当它激发人们想象时，它就会变得强大
a new future.
[AI] 新的未来。
And although every place I've worked is unique.
[AI] 虽然我工作过的每个地方都是独一无二的。
it all boils down to one thing:
[AI] 这一切归结为一件事：
if people can sit together. they can dream together.
[AI] 如果人们能坐在一起。他们可以一起梦想。
Thank you.
[AI] 非常感谢。